Milan Grahovac

IT Support Specialist

12459 Berlin0152 5464 9612

☑ grahovac85@gmail.com

github.com/milangrahovac

Summary

I am an IT Support Specialist with 2.5 years of experience in assisting users in person and remotely. I have experience in managing users' accounts, onboarding, and offboarding users. One of my duties is also to write and update HelpDesk documentation.

I have basic knowledge of software engineering topics. At the moment, I am learning Go and Python. You can find some examples of my Python code for the LeetCode coding challenges here: https://github.com/milangrahovac/leetcode-python.

I am open to new opportunities for long-term professional development and growth.

Skills

- Problem-solving oriented approach
- Communication and empathy to users' needs
- Understanding of PC/Mac hardware setup and configuration
- Ability to learn new things quickly
- Google Admin console
- Lastpass administration
- MS Office 365 administration
- Meraki

- Command line tools (Linux, MacOS)
- Git
- Python
- Go (basics)
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript (basics)

Work experience

N26 GmbH - Berlin, Germany

IT Helpdesk Specialist - Site Coordinator

- Coordinating projects with stakeholders.
- Manage users' accounts and rights.
- Install, configure, and upgrade PC/Mac software.
- Assist with onboarding of new users.
- Keep inventory of all equipment.
- Diagnose and troubleshooting tech problems.
- Provide support for users in person and via Slack/Google meet.

Mardor human resources GmbH - Berlin, Germany

IVI

May 2018 - September 2018

December 2018 - now

Electrician

• Installation and maintenance of electrical systems.

SZTR Janj - Zrenjanin, Serbia

2008 - 2016

Office Assistant

Assisted in administrative duties.

SZTR Janj - Zrenjanin, Serbia

2004 - 2008

Electrician

- Maintained and repaired electrical systems.
- Diagnosed and solved issues on various electrical systems.
- Adhered to all safety rules and regulations.

Languages

Serbian (Native)

Russian (Upper Intermediate)

English (Upper Intermediate)

German (Beginner)

Education

Master in management of business communications

2008 - 2012

University of Novi Sad "Mihajlo Pupin" Technical Faculty

Management of business communications

2004 - 2008

University of Novi Sad "Mihajlo Pupin"Technical Faculty

Electrical technician for automatic control

2000 - 2004

Electrical and Construction School "Nikola Tesla"

Additional programs and courses

Coursera - Google IT Support (5 courses)

Coursera - Google IT Automation with Python (7 courses)

Coursera - Google GSuite/Workspace (4 courses)

Coursera - AWS Cloud Technical Essentials

GeekBrains - Go Developer (in progress - 4/14 courses)

You can find more details and certificates on my LinkedIn page: https://www.linkedin.com/in/milan-grahovac/.

Created with **TVisualCV**